May 11th is World Keffia Day and it is a day to wear your keffia to show solidarity
to Palestine. And though you may not have your keffia by tomorrow, one place where you can
get your keffia and support a Palestinian craftsperson is from Hebron with love. You know,
when we think about how many of us really didn't even understand the immensity of what it means
to support Palestine until October 7th, we understand that so many of us now have come
on board and we want to be able to show our love, to show our respect and to show our solidarity on
a regular basis. And you can do that by simply wearing your keffia, wearing it boldly, wearing
it proudly and wearing it loudly. So you can get your keffias from a number of places, but you can
also make sure to support those in Palestine who are continuing to make them like from Hebron with
love, free Palestine.